{
  "DeckName": "Kanji Vol1",
  "LanguageCode": "ja-JP",
  "DeckEnabled": false,
  "Cards": [
    {
      "Question": "一",
      "Narration": "ichi",
      "Answer": "one"
    },
    {
      "Question": "二",
      "Narration": "ni",
      "Answer": "two"
    },
    {
      "Question": "三",
      "Narration": "san",
      "Answer": "three"
    },
    {
      "Question": "四",
      "Narration": "shi",
      "Answer": "four"
    },
    {
      "Question": "五",
      "Narration": "go",
      "Answer": "five"
    },
    {
      "Question": "六",
      "Narration": "roku",
      "Answer": "six"
    },
    {
      "Question": "七",
      "Narration": "shichi",
      "Answer": "seven"
    },
    {
      "Question": "八",
      "Narration": "hachi",
      "Answer": "eight"
    },
    {
      "Question": "九",
      "Narration": "kyuu",
      "Answer": "nine"
    },
    {
      "Question": "十",
      "Narration": "juu",
      "Answer": "ten"
    },
    {
      "Question": "百",
      "Narration": "hyaku",
      "Answer": "hundred"
    },
    {
      "Question": "千",
      "Narration": "sen",
      "Answer": "thousand"
    },
    {
      "Question": "万",
      "Narration": "man",
      "Answer": "ten thousand"
    },
    {
      "Question": "白",
      "Narration": "shiro",
      "Answer": "white"
    },
    {
      "Question": "黒",
      "Narration": "kuro",
      "Answer": "black"
    },
    {
      "Question": "赤",
      "Narration": "aka",
      "Answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "Question": "青",
      "Narration": "ao",
      "Answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "Question": "黄",
      "Narration": "ki",
      "Answer": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "Question": "上",
      "Narration": "ue",
      "Answer": "above | top"
    },
    {
      "Question": "下",
      "Narration": "shita",
      "Answer": "below | bottom"
    },
    {
      "Question": "左",
      "Narration": "hidari",
      "Answer": "left"
    },
    {
      "Question": "右",
      "Narration": "migi",
      "Answer": "right"
    },
    {
      "Question": "前",
      "Narration": "mae",
      "Answer": "before | front"
    },
    {
      "Question": "後",
      "Narration": "go",
      "Answer": "after | back"
    },
    {
      "Question": "東",
      "Narration": "higashi",
      "Answer": "east"
    },
    {
      "Question": "西",
      "Narration": "nishi",
      "Answer": "west"
    },
    {
      "Question": "南",
      "Narration": "minami",
      "Answer": "south"
    },
    {
      "Question": "北",
      "Narration": "kita",
      "Answer": "north"
    },
    {
      "Question": "父",
      "Narration": "chichi",
      "Answer": "father"
    },
    {
      "Question": "母",
      "Narration": "haha",
      "Answer": "mother"
    },
    {
      "Question": "男",
      "Narration": "otoko",
      "Answer": "man | male"
    },
    {
      "Question": "女",
      "Narration": "onna",
      "Answer": "woman | female"
    },
    {
      "Question": "友",
      "Narration": "tomo",
      "Answer": "friend"
    },
    {
      "Question": "人",
      "Narration": "hito",
      "Answer": "person | people"
    },
    {
      "Question": "子",
      "Narration": "ko",
      "Answer": "child | offspring"
    },
    {
      "Question": "日",
      "Narration": "nichi",
      "Answer": "sun | day"
    },
    {
      "Question": "月",
      "Narration": "tsuki",
      "Answer": "month | moon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "火",
      "Narration": "hi",
      "Answer": "fire"
    },
    {
      "Question": "水",
      "Narration": "mizu",
      "Answer": "water"
    },
    {
      "Question": "木",
      "Narration": "ki",
      "Answer": "tree | wood"
    },
    {
      "Question": "金",
      "Narration": "kin",
      "Answer": "gold"
    },
    {
      "Question": "土",
      "Narration": "tsuchi",
      "Answer": "earth | ground"
    },
    {
      "Question": "天",
      "Narration": "ten",
      "Answer": "heaven | sky"
    },
    {
      "Question": "国",
      "Narration": "kuni",
      "Answer": "country | nation"
    },
    {
      "Question": "本",
      "Narration": "hon",
      "Answer": "book"
    },
    {
      "Question": "間",
      "Narration": "kan",
      "Answer": "interval | space"
    },
    {
      "Question": "年",
      "Narration": "nen",
      "Answer": "year"
    },
    {
      "Question": "時",
      "Narration": "ji",
      "Answer": "time | hour"
    },
    {
      "Question": "今",
      "Narration": "ima",
      "Answer": "now | present"
    },
    {
      "Question": "先",
      "Narration": "saki",
      "Answer": "previous | ahead"
    },
    {
      "Question": "来",
      "Narration": "kuru",
      "Answer": "come | next"
    },
    {
      "Question": "出",
      "Narration": "deru",
      "Answer": "exit | leave"
    },
    {
      "Question": "入",
      "Narration": "iri",
      "Answer": "enter | insert"
    },
    {
      "Question": "行",
      "Narration": "iku",
      "Answer": "go | line"
    },
    {
      "Question": "見",
      "Narration": "miru",
      "Answer": "see | look"
    },
    {
      "Question": "聞",
      "Narration": "kiku",
      "Answer": "listen | ask"
    },
    {
      "Question": "話",
      "Narration": "hanasu",
      "Answer": "talk | story"
    },
    {
      "Question": "読",
      "Narration": "yomu",
      "Answer": "read | study"
    },
    {
      "Question": "書",
      "Narration": "kaku",
      "Answer": "write"
    },
    {
      "Question": "食",
      "Narration": "taberu",
      "Answer": "eat | meal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "車",
      "Narration": "kuruma",
      "Answer": "car | vehicle"
    },
    {
      "Question": "校",
      "Narration": "kou",
      "Answer": "school | examination"
    },
    {
      "Question": "学",
      "Narration": "gaku",
      "Answer": "study | learning"
    },
    {
      "Question": "高",
      "Narration": "takai",
      "Answer": "high | tall"
    },
    {
      "Question": "円",
      "Narration": "en",
      "Answer": "yen | circle"
    },
    {
      "Question": "小",
      "Narration": "shou",
      "Answer": "small | little"
    },
    {
      "Question": "大",
      "Narration": "dai",
      "Answer": "big | large"
    },
    {
      "Question": "長",
      "Narration": "chou",
      "Answer": "long | leader"
    },
    {
      "Question": "半",
      "Narration": "han",
      "Answer": "half | semi"
    },
    {
      "Question": "何",
      "Narration": "nani",
      "Answer": "what | how many"
    },
    {
      "Question": "毎",
      "Narration": "mai",
      "Answer": "every | each"
    },
    {
      "Question": "気",
      "Narration": "ki",
      "Answer": "spirit | mind"
    },
    {
      "Question": "名",
      "Narration": "na",
      "Answer": "name | famous"
    },
    {
      "Question": "山",
      "Narration": "yama",
      "Answer": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "Question": "川",
      "Narration": "kawa",
      "Answer": "river | stream"
    },
    {
      "Question": "草",
      "Narration": "kusa",
      "Answer": "grass"
    },
    {
      "Question": "花",
      "Narration": "hana",
      "Answer": "flower"
    },
    {
      "Question": "虫",
      "Narration": "mushi",
      "Answer": "insect"
    },
    {
      "Question": "鳥",
      "Narration": "tori",
      "Answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "Question": "犬",
      "Narration": "inu",
      "Answer": "dog"
    },
    {
      "Question": "猫",
      "Narration": "neko",
      "Answer": "cat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "魚",
      "Narration": "sakana",
      "Answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "米",
      "Narration": "kome",
      "Answer": "rice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "水",
      "Narration": "mizu",
      "Answer": "water"
    },
    {
      "Question": "茶",
      "Narration": "cha",
      "Answer": "tea"
    },
    {
      "Question": "酒",
      "Narration": "sake",
      "Answer": "alcohol | sake"
    },
    {
      "Question": "飯",
      "Narration": "meshi",
      "Answer": "meal | cooked rice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "肉",
      "Narration": "niku",
      "Answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "豚",
      "Narration": "buta",
      "Answer": "pork"
    },
    {
      "Question": "鳥",
      "Narration": "tori",
      "Answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "Question": "魚",
      "Narration": "sakana",
      "Answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "牛",
      "Narration": "ushi",
      "Answer": "cow"
    },
    {
      "Question": "馬",
      "Narration": "uma",
      "Answer": "horse"
    },
    {
      "Question": "鳥居",
      "Narration": "torii",
      "Answer": "Shinto shrine gate"
    },
    {
      "Question": "鳥類",
      "Narration": "chourui",
      "Answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "Question": "牛肉",
      "Narration": "gyuniku",
      "Answer": "beef"
    },
    {
      "Question": "牛乳",
      "Narration": "gyuunyuu",
      "Answer": "milk"
    },
    {
      "Question": "魚介類",
      "Narration": "gyokairui",
      "Answer": "seafood"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家畜",
      "Narration": "kachiku",
      "Answer": "livestock"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家畜",
      "Narration": "kachiku",
      "Answer": "livestock"
    },
    {
      "Question": "魚介類",
      "Narration": "gyokairui",
      "Answer": "seafood"
    },
    {
      "Question": "野菜",
      "Narration": "yasai",
      "Answer": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "Question": "野原",
      "Narration": "nohara",
      "Answer": "field"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家屋",
      "Narration": "kaya",
      "Answer": "house"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家具",
      "Narration": "kagu",
      "Answer": "furniture"
    },
    {
      "Question": "住家",
      "Narration": "juukya",
      "Answer": "household"
    },
    {
      "Question": "植物",
      "Narration": "shokubutsu",
      "Answer": "plant"
    },
    {
      "Question": "植物",
      "Narration": "shokubutsu",
      "Answer": "plant"
    },
    {
      "Question": "果物",
      "Narration": "kudamono",
      "Answer": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "実物",
      "Narration": "jitsubutsu",
      "Answer": "actual thing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "食べ物",
      "Narration": "tabemono",
      "Answer": "food"
    },
    {
      "Question": "飲み物",
      "Narration": "nomimono",
      "Answer": "drink"
    },
    {
      "Question": "動物",
      "Narration": "doubutsu",
      "Answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "動物",
      "Narration": "doubutsu",
      "Answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "水族館",
      "Narration": "suizokukan",
      "Answer": "aquarium"
    },
    {
      "Question": "動物園",
      "Narration": "doubutsuen",
      "Answer": "zoo"
    },
    {
      "Question": "動物園",
      "Narration": "doubutsuen",
      "Answer": "zoo"
    },
    {
      "Question": "鳥居",
      "Narration": "torii",
      "Answer": "Shinto shrine gate"
    },
    {
      "Question": "鳥類",
      "Narration": "chourui",
      "Answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家畜",
      "Narration": "kachiku",
      "Answer": "livestock"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家畜",
      "Narration": "kachiku",
      "Answer": "livestock"
    },
    {
      "Question": "魚介類",
      "Narration": "gyokairui",
      "Answer": "seafood"
    },
    {
      "Question": "野菜",
      "Narration": "yasai",
      "Answer": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "Question": "野原",
      "Narration": "nohara",
      "Answer": "field"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家屋",
      "Narration": "kaya",
      "Answer": "house"
    },
    {
      "Question": "家具",
      "Narration": "kagu",
      "Answer": "furniture"
    },
    {
      "Question": "住家",
      "Narration": "juukya",
      "Answer": "household"
    },
    {
      "Question": "植物",
      "Narration": "shokubutsu",
      "Answer": "plant"
    },
    {
      "Question": "植物",
      "Narration": "shokubutsu",
      "Answer": "plant"
    },
    {
      "Question": "果物",
      "Narration": "kudamono",
      "Answer": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "実物",
      "Narration": "jitsubutsu",
      "Answer": "actual thing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "食べ物",
      "Narration": "tabemono",
      "Answer": "food"
    },
    {
      "Question": "飲み物",
      "Narration": "nomimono",
      "Answer": "drink"
    },
    {
      "Question": "動物",
      "Narration": "doubutsu",
      "Answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "動物",
      "Narration": "doubutsu",
      "Answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "水族館",
      "Narration": "suizokukan",
      "Answer": "aquarium"
    },
    {
      "Question": "動物園",
      "Narration": "doubutsuen",
      "Answer": "zoo"
    }
  ]
}